

Dukuh Street, RT. 01/05 Karangsatria, North Tambun, Kab Bekasi, West Java. padiriski25@gmail.com

M RISKI PADILAH

Summary

I am a graduate of high school majoring in Software Engineering with a focus on front-end development. Experienced in HTML, CSS, JS, and React.js, as well as PHP skills. I have worked freelance on various projects, building responsive and interactive websites. I always try to provide efficient and result-oriented solutions.

Experience

Coding & Robotics Teacher, K ROBO

Ags 2024 - Present

- Teaches the basics of web programming, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to middle and high school students.
- Guide students in practical projects, such as creating simple websites to interactive web applications.
- Introduces the basic concepts of robotics, including sensors, motors, and microcontrollers such as Arduino.
- Develop learning modules and innovative teaching materials that focus on the practical application of coding theory.

Freelancer, Glassdoor

Apr 2024 - Present

- Design an attractive and functional user interface (UI) with user experience (UX) in mind.
- Developing website appearance using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and the React.js framework.
- Automatically fetch and collect data from various web sources.
- Organize data into a format that is easy to understand and can be integrated into systems or applications according to client needs.

Education

Software Engineering, SMKN 6 Bekasi City

Jul 2021 - Mei 2024

- Competency test on "School Digital Library".
- take part in student level wrestling championship at POPDA XIII JABAR 2023.

Skills

- Front-End Development
- Data Scraping
- UI/UX Designer

Certificate

Certificate of Basic React.js by Dicoding, 2024.

Certificate of Competency by CV Inspirasi Software, 2024.